Guide to the James Gamble Rogers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
James Gamble Rogers papers
1885-1895
MS 396
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
44
(71 boxes)
The papers consist of photographs, plans, drawings, specifications, job files, correspondence, contracts, and printed material, which relate to architectural projects, particularly residences and government, church, hospital, and school buildings, designed by James Gamble Rogers, or the firms of Hale and Rogers, James Gamble Rogers, Inc., and Rogers and Butler. The most extensive files are for buildings on the Yale University campus, but there are also substantial files on the Aetna Life Insurance Company home office, the Columbia-Presbyterian Hospital, the New Haven Post Office and Court House, the Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, and buildings on the campuses of Northwestern University and Columbia University. The papers also include personal papers of James Gamble Rogers and his son Francis Day Rogers.
Rogers, James Gamble, 1867-1947
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the James Gamble Rogers estate, circa. 1960s, and of Pauline Rogers, 1987 and 1994.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
11.75 linear feet (29 boxes)
Dates: 1913-1941
The James Gamble Rogers Papers came to Yale, probably in the late 1960s, and were first stored in the Plan Room at Buildings and Grounds, 20 Ashmun Street. Some papers were discarded by that office; others, including all plans, sections, and elevations for Yale buildings are still in use there. Some papers, especially detail drawings, were transferred to Manuscripts and Archives, and subsequently all architectural drawings for Yale buildings were placed in the Architectural Archives Collection.
What remains is an uneven and gap-ridden collection of office files; nonetheless it documents phases of the design and planning of much of the Yale campus and half a dozen of Rogers' other projects in New York. The papers are arranged by building or project; they include job files, schedules of hardware, specifications, photographs and drawings, but the files are not complete for any one building.
The job files for the Yale buildings consist largely of correspondence and other papers exchanged with the contractor, Marc Eidlitz & Son of New York City. There is also correspondence with consulting engineer Hollis French, of New Haven and Boston, who drew up many of the specifications.
The photographs are mostly of models for ornamental stonework, sculpted by René P. Chambellan. There are also many photographs of mantels, and photographs of buildings which Rogers hoped to imitate in some feature, and of people whom he planned to represent in the decorations.
More extensive Rogers' correspondence and architectural records can be found in the following collections in Manuscripts and Archives:
Architectural Archives --- YRG 46
Treasurer's Records --- 5 - B
Services Bureau --- 5 - I-9
Corporation Committee on Architectural Plan --- 1-E
Presidential Records: Arthur T. Hadley --- 2 - A-13
Presidential Records: James R. Angell --- 2 - A-14
Presidential Records: Charles Seymour --- 2 - A-15
Records of the Provost --- 3 - A
Records of the University Librarian --- 32 - C
George Parmly Day Papers --- MS. Grp. No. 174
James H. Penniman Papers --- 9
Anson Phelps Stokes Papers --- 299
Biographical / Historical
James Gamble Rogers was born on March 3, 1867, in Bryants Station, Kentucky. He received a B.A. degree from Yale University in 1889 and a Diplo?me d'Architecte from the École Nationale et Spéciale des Beaux-Arts in Paris in 1899. He began his architectural practice in New York City in 1905 and was responsible for numerous residences and government, church, hospital, and school buildings. Rogers died on October 1, 1947.
Architecture -- United States; Church architecture -- United States; Public buildings -- United States; School buildings -- United States; East Lyme (Conn.); New Haven (Conn.) -- Buildings, structures, etc.; Architectural drawings; Photoprints; Architects; French, Hollis, 1868-1940; Harkness, Edward Stephen, 1874-1940; Lohmann, Carl A. (Carl Albert), 1887-; Milliken, Seth Mellen, 1836-1920; Rogers, Francis Day; Rogers, James Gamble, 1867-1947; Aetna Life Insurance Company (Hartford, Conn.) -- Buildings; Berkeley College (Yale University); Beta Theta Pi. Phi Chi Chapter (Yale University); Branford College (Yale University); Columbia University ( Buildings); Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center; Davenport College (Yale University); Delta Kappa Epsilon. Phi Chapter (Yale University); Hale and Rogers; James Gamble Rogers, Inc; Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University); Marc Eidlitz & Son; Miriam Osborn Memorial Home Association (Harrison, N.Y.); Northwestern University (Evanston, Ill.) -- Buildings; Psi Upsilon. Beta chapter, Yale University; Rogers and Butler; Saybrook College (Yale University); Southern Baptist Theological Seminary -- Buildings; Timothy Dwight College (Yale University); Yale Club of New York City; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Crew; Yale University. Graduate School; Yale University. Library; Yale University. Memorial Quadrangle
- Inventory
  - Yale buildings
    - Berkeley College
      - Job files correspondence
        - Eidlitz, Marc & Son, 1933-1937 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
        - G-Sc, Circa 1931-1937 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
        - Seymour, Charles, 1931-1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Si-Y, Circa 1931-1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence of Hollis French, 1931-1935 (Box 2, Folder 10-14)
      - Job files
        - Changes, 1931-1934 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - Data, 1931-1937 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
      - Specifications, 1932-1933 September (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
      - Specifications, 1933 October-1934 (Box 4, Folder 21-25)
      - Photographs
        - German Picture Room, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
        - Mantels, 1933-1934, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
        - Miscellaneous, 1932-1933, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Beta Theta Pi Fraternity House, 204 York St.: specifications, 1926, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Boat Houses: specifications
      - Gales Ferry Boat House, Gales Ferry, Conn, 1914, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Bob Cook Boat House, Derby, Conn., 1923, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Branford and Saybrook Colleges (Box 5)
      General
      See also: box 17, folders 140-147
      - Specifications, 1932 April-October (Box 5, Folder 31-33)
      - Specifications, 1932 November-1933, undated (Box 5, Folder 34-39)
      - Photographs, 1932-1933 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon Fraternity House, 232 York St.: specifications, 1925, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Timothy Dwight College
      - Job files correspondence
        - Eidlitz, Marc & Son, 1934-1937, undated (Box 7, Folder 42-47)
        - Eidlitz, Marc & Son: proposals, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 48-49)
        - F, 1934-1936 (Box 8, Folder 50)
        - Lohmann, Carl A., 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 51)
        - P-Y, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 52)
        - Correspondence of Hollis French, 1934-1936 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Job files
        - Brick, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 54)
        - Building permits, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 55)
        - Cabinet work, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 56)
        - Card catalog, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 57)
        - Carpentry, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 58)
        - Changes: general, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 59)
        - Changes: plans, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 60)
        - Clocks, 1933-1935 (Box 8, Folder 61)
        - Daily reports, 1934-1936 (Box 8, Folder 62-63)
        - Data, 1933-1935 (Box 8, Folder 64)
        - Doors, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 65)
        - Elevators, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 66)
        - Engineers' bills, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 67)
        - Glass and glazing, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 68)
        - Hardware, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 69)
        - Heating and ventilation, 1933-1936 (Box 9, Folder 70-72)
        - Iron: miscellaneous, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 73)
        - Iron: ornamental, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 74)
        - Kalamein work, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 75)
        - Kitchen and kitchenette, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 76)
        - Landscaping, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 77)
        - Mantels, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 78)
        - Masonry, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 79)
        - Master's house, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 80)
        - Mill work, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 81)
        - Models, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 82)
        - Orders, estimates and bills, 1934-1935, undated (Box 9, Folder 83-84)
        - Painting, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 85)
        - Partitions, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 86)
        - Plastering, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 87)
        - Plumbing, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 88)
        - Professional bills, 1935-1937 (Box 10, Folder 89)
        - Proposed bidders, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 90)
        - Refrigeration, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 91)
        - Roofing, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 92)
        - Stone, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 93)
        - Structural steel, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 94)
        - Subcontractors: orders, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 95)
        - Subcontractors: tabulations of bids, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 96)
        - Surveying-civil engineering, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 97)
        - Tile and terrazzo, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 98)
        - Wallpaper, 1935, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 99)
        - Weatherstripping, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 100)
        - Windows and frames, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 101)
        - Miscellaneous, 1934-1936 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Schedules of hardware, 1935 January (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Schedules of hardware, 1935 May-July (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Schedules of proposals, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Specifications, 1933-1935, undated (Box 11, Folder 106-109)
      - Photographs: mantels, miscellaneous, 1933-1935, undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Jonathan Edwards College
      - Schedules of hardware, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 111)
      - Specifications, 1924-1925, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 112-115)
      - Specifications, 1932-1933, undated (Box 13, Folder 116-117)
      - Specifications: memoranda specifications: draughting room copies, 1924-1925, undated (Box 13, Folder 118)
      - Specifications: negatives, 1924-1925, undated (Box 13, Folder 119)
      - Photographs: miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Elm Dormitories
      See also: boxes 24-25, folders 208-216
      - Specifications, 1929 June-October (Box 13, Folder 121)
      - Specifications, 1929 November-1930, 1937, undated (Box 14, Folder 122)
      - Photographic models, 1932, undated (Box 14, Folder 123-124)
    - Graduate School
      - Schedules of hardware, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 125-126)
      - Specifications, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 127-128)
      - Specifications, 1931 January-September (Box 15, Folder 129-134)
      - Specifications, 1931 October-1932, undated (Box 16, Folder 135-136)
      - Specifications: negatives, 1930, undated (Box 16, Folder 137)
      - Photographs
        - Furniture, undated (Box 16, Folder 138)
        - Models, 1930-1931, undated (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - Memorial Quadrangle (Box 16)
      See also: boxes 5-6, folders 31-40
      - Schedules of hardware, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 140)
      - Specifications, 1917-1921, undated (Box 17, Folder 141-146)
      - Correspondence re: gates, cost of, 1922 November 3 (Box 17, Folder 146A)
      - Photographs: Gould Law School, undated (Box 17, Folder 147)
    - Pierson and Davenport Colleges
      - Schedules of construction and finish, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 148)
      - Schedules of hardware, 1930-1932 (Box 17, Folder 149)
      - Specifications, 1930 May-July (Box 17, Folder 150-151)
      - Specifications, 1930 August-1932 June 14 (Box 18, Folder 152-162)
      - Specifications, 1932 June 27-1933, n.d (Box 19, Folder 163-170)
      - Photographs
        - Models, with model schedule, 1931, undated (Box 19, Folder 171)
        - Models, undated (Box 20, Folder 172)
    - Psi Upsilon Fraternity House, 224 York St.
      - Job files: bids and estimates, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 173)
      - Specifications, 1926-1927, undated (Box 20, Folder 174-175)
    - Sterling Law Buildings
      - Schedules of hardware, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 176)
      - Specifications, 1929-1931, undated (Box 20, Folder 177-181)
      - Photographs: models, miscellaneous, 1930, undated (Box 21, Folder 182)
    - Sterling Memorial Library
      - Job files correspondence
        - B-C; Eidlitz, Marc, & Son, 1926-1929 (Box 21, Folder 183)
        - Eidlitz, Marc, & Son, 1926-1929 (Box 21, Folder 184-185)
        - F-K, 1925-1929 (Box 21, Folder 186)
      - Job files: subcontractors: orders, contracts, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 187-189)
      - "Notes of Trip Inspecting Libraries", 1929 (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Notes for Yale Library, 1928-1929 (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Schedules of hardware, 1927-1930 (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Schedules of models, notes, 1928-1931 (Box 22, Folder 192)
      - Outline specifications, miscellaneous, undated (Box 22, Folder 193)
      - Specifications, 1926-1928 May (Box 22, Folder 194-198)
      - Specifications, 1928 June-1930 (Box 23, Folder 199-207)
    - Trumbull College
      See also: boxes 13-14, folders 121-124, other buildings
      - Schedules of hardware, 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 208)
      - Specifications, 1931-1933 (Box 24, Folder 209-215)
      - Photographs: models, 1933 (Box 25, Folder 216)
  - Other buildings
    - College of Physicians and Surgeons, Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center, N.Y.C.: drawings, 1926-1930 (Box 25, Folder 217)
    - Eye Institute, The Medical Center (Columbia-Presbyterian, N.Y.C.?): equipment specifications, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 218)
    - Farwell Cottage (N.Y.C.?): heating specifications, undated (Box 25, Folder 219)
    - Alterations of a house for music studio and residence of Dr. S.M. Milliken, 947 Madison Avenue, N.Y.C.: drawings, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 220)
    - Miriam Osborn Memorial Home Association, 1934 addition, Harrison and Rye, N.Y.: specifications, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 221)
    - Yale Club building, N.Y.C.: specifications, 1913-1915, undated (Box 26, Folder 222-228)
  - Architectural reference files-postcards, undated (Box 27–28)
  - Hogeboom, Charles F.: "Pencil sketches and tracings of classical details" (2 volumes), 1890-1892, 1897, undated (Box 29)
- Additional Material, 1890s-1984; Accession 1988-M-016; 31.75 linear feet (41 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Received from Pauline Rogers, 1987 Jul 21
  Addition inventory by Murat Dogruer and Diane E. Kaplan 1988 April
  This addition to the James Gamble Rogers Papers consists of photographs, plans, drawings, financial records, correspondence, and printed material relating to architectural projects designed by James Gamble Rogers or the firms of Hale and Rogers, James Gamble Rogers, Inc., and Rogers and Butler. The most extensive files are for buildings on the Yale University campus, but there are also substantial files on the Aetna Life Insurance Company home office, the Columbia-Presbyterian Hospital, the New Haven Post Office and Court House, the Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, and buildings on the campuses of Northwestern University and Columbia University. The addition also includes some personal papers of James Gamble Rogers and his son, Francis Day Rogers.
  The addition is arranged in four sections by record type: Drawings, photographs and construction notes; Published material; Legal and financial records; Personal papers. Papers about a particular project may be found in each section except Personal papers. Photographs and reproductions of plans and drawings comprise the bulk of the addition. The papers include very few original drawings.
  The section Drawings, photographs, and construction notes begins with architectural reference files which contain photographs and plans for buildings not designed by James Gamble Rogers or his firms. Rogers collected some of these as a student at the École Nationale et Spéciale des Beaux-Arts in Paris in the 1890s. Others relate to buildings on the Yale campus.
  The remainder of the section is composed of drawings, reproductions of drawings, construction notes, construction photographs, and photographs showing completed projects. These materials are arranged alphabetically by project name, with the more voluminous Yale project files preceding the files for all other buildings. Amongst the files for the non-Yale projects are materials relating to church, government, hospital, and school buidings as well as individual residences. Materials in the files are arranged by size, in either flat storage containers for large photographs and drawings or in upright files for notes or other items not larger than 8½" x l5". For any particular building, therefore, there may be two listings in this section, either under the headings "Flat" or "Upright".
  Published material is also arranged alphabetically by project name. The files contain articles, clippings, and brochures about building plans, construction, and completed projects.
  The Legal and financial records includes numerous contract files containing correspondence, contracts, and some bills and receipts. These files are arranged alphabetically by project name with some general files for "Residences" and "Schools" interspersed. More building projects are documented in this section than in the two preceding sections. The section also includes minutes, payrolls, and other financial records for the firms of Hale and Rogers and James Gamble Rogers, Inc.
  Personal papers is composed of correspondence and memorabilia of James Gamble Rogers, as well as some papers of his son, Francis Day Rogers. The latter includes a solicitations notebook for the St. Paul's School Alumni Association and minutes and other records of the Federation of East Lyme Beaches.
  - Drawings, photographs, and construction notes
    - Architectural reference files, [ca. 1890s-1930s] (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
      See also: box 40
    - Yale buildings
      - Flat
        - Alpha Delta Phi, [ca. 1928] (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Alpha Sigma Phi, [undated] (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Berkeley, [1933-1934] (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
        - Berkeley, [1933-1934] (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - Branford College (Box 3, Folder 14-16)
          See also: box 19
          General note
          See also: box 18
        - Branford College, [ca. 1917-1920] (Box 11, Box 12, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 4, Folder 17-44, Box 5, Box 6)
        - Timothy Dwight College, [ca. 1934-1935] (Box 12, Folder 45)
        - Timothy Dwight College, [ca. 1934-1935] (Box 13, Folder 46-47)
        - Graduate School, [ca. 1932] (Box 13, Folder 48)
        - Memorial Quadrangle
          See: box 3, folder 14-16
        - Sterling Law Buildings, [ca. 1927-1931] (Box 13, Folder 49-50)
          See also: box 20
        - Sterling Memorial Library, [ca. 1926-1929] (Box 14, Folder 51-53)
        - Sterling Memorial Library, [ca. 1928-1930] (Box 15, Folder 54-56)
        - Sterling Memorial Library, [ca. 1930] (Box 16, Folder 57-60)
        - Trumbull College, [ca. 1928-1932] (Box 16, Folder 61)
        - Yale Theater, [undated] (Box 16, Folder 62)
          See also: box 21
        - General (Box 17, Folder 63-70)
          See also: box 41
      - Upright
        - Branford College, [ca. 1917-1920] (Box 18, Folder 71-79)
          See also: box 3
        - Branford College, [ca. 1917-1920] (Box 19, Folder 80)
        - Sterling Law Buildings, [ca. 1927-1931] (Box 20, Folder 81-83)
        - Sterling Memorial Library, [ca. 1926-1930] (Box 20, Folder 84)
          See also: boxes 13-16
        - Sterling Memorial Library, [ca. 1935] (Box 21, Folder 85-91)
          See also: box 16
    - Other buildings
      - Flat
        - Our Church of All Angels, New York City, [undated] (Box 22, Folder 92)
        - Aetna Life Insurance Co. Home Office, Hartford (Conn.), [ca. 1923-1924] (Box 22, Folder 93-95)
        - Caspany Research Building, (N.Y.), 1959 (Box 22, Folder 96)
        - Chicago (Ill.), apartment buildings, [undated] (Box 22, Folder 97)
        - Colgate Rochester Divinity School
          See: box 27
        - Columbia Presbyterian Hospital
          See: box 23, folder 106
        - Columbia University Library, [ca. 1932-1933] (Box 22, Folder 98-99)
        - Connecticut College Chapel, New London (Conn.), [undated] (Box 22, Folder 100)
        - Cornell University: F.W. Olm Hall Medical College, [undated] (Box 22, Folder 101)
        - Crane Company Exhibit Buildings, Atlantic City, (N.J.)
        - Featherbed Lane Church, Bronx (N.Y.), [undated] (Box 22, Folder 102)
        - Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church, New York City, [ca. 1916-1917, 1931] (Box 22, Folder 103)
        - Mystic Chapel
          See: box 27, folder 149
        - New Haven (Conn.) Post Office and Court House, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 104)
          See also: box 27-29
        - New Orleans (La.) Post Office and Court House Buildings, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 105)
        - New York City: medical center, [ca. 1930s] (Box 23, Folder 106)
          See also: box 29, folder 160-161
        - New York University: building for Wall Street Center, [undated] (Box 23, Folder 107)
        - Northwestern University, [ca. 1923-1925] (Box 23, Folder 108-111)
        - Northwestern University, [ca. 1922-1923] (Box 24, Folder 112)
        - Ossining (N.Y.) Senior-Junior High School, [undated] (Box 24, Folder 113)
        - Residences
          - Day, Lake Forest (Ill.), [undated] (Box 24, Folder 114)
          - Dick, A.B., [undated] (Box 24, Folder 115)
          - Fakewell, A.L., Lake Forest (Ill.) (Box 24, Folder 116)
          - Feuer, New York City, [undated] (Box 24, Folder 117)
          - Harkness, W.L., 1913 (Box 24, Folder 118)
          - Harkness, New York City, [undated] (Box 24, Folder 119)
          - Huntington, Mill Neck, Long Island (N.Y.), 1928 (Box 24, Folder 120)
          - Ide, George E., Locust Valley, Long Island (N.Y.), 1915 (Box 24, Folder 121)
          - Isham (Box 24, Folder 122)
          - Page, F.H., Highland Park, (Ill.), [undated] (Box 24, Folder 123)
          - Robbins, F.H., Lake Forest, (Ill.), [undated] (Box 24, Folder 124)
          - Rosden, John, [undated] (Box 24, Folder 125)
          - Thomson, Peter (Ill.), [undated] (Box 25, Folder 126)
          - Thornton, Cincinatti (Ohio), [undated] (Box 25, Folder 127)
          - Unidentified, Illinois, [undated] (Box 25, Folder 128)
          - Unidentified, [undated] (Box 25, Folder 129-130)
        - Riegel Paper Company: community building, Milford (N.J.), [undated] (Box 25, Folder 131)
        - Rockefeller (John D.) Fine Arts Building, Spelman College, Atlanta (Ga.), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 132)
        - Shelby County Courthouse, Memphis, (Tenn.) (Box 25, Folder 133)
        - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, Louisville (Ky.), 1924-1926 (Box 25, Folder 134)
        - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, Louisville (Ky.), [ca. 1923-1926] (Box 26, Folder 135)
        - Strauss Mausoleum, Woodlawn (N.Y.), 1929 (Box 26, Folder 136)
        - Taft School, Watertown (Conn.), [ca. 1926] (Box 26, Folder 137)
        - Union Theological Seminary, New York City, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 138)
        - University of Chicago, Emmons Blare Hall, School of Education, [undated] (Box 26, Folder 139)
        - University of Chicago, Lexington Avenue School, [undated] (Box 26, Folder 140)
        - "A House for the United States Embassy at Paris,", [undated] (Box 26, Folder 141)
        - Yale and Town Mfg., Co., Stamford (Conn.), [undated] (Box 26, Folder 142)
        - Yale Club, New York City, 1914-1915 (Box 26, Folder 143)
        - Yale Hospital, China, [undated] (Box 26, Folder 144)
      - Upright